<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on KayEssPea Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on KayEssPea Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Keisha S Perkins</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 10:34:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.keishasperkins.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Powerful Illustrator Shape Builder Tool</title>
      <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/04/02/the-powerful-illustrator-shape-builder-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 10:34:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/04/02/the-powerful-illustrator-shape-builder-tool/</guid>
      <description>When I began to foray into Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Creative Suite, I was using Photoshop for everything. Need a logo for lots of uses? Just deliver a huge PNG! Want to draw a nice crisp illustration? Photoshop&amp;rsquo;s pen tool works just fine for that, right?
Photoshop was my one-stop for everything I needed, though none of what I needed was what Photoshop was created for. It was some time before I even considered using any of Adobe&amp;rsquo;s many great pieces of software that actually suited my needs, like Illustrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Five Sources for Free Assets</title>
      <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/03/18/top-five-freebie-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 11:08:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/03/18/top-five-freebie-sources/</guid>
      <description>I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair to say that all of us have at one time or another needed to get a job done on a small&amp;ndash;or sometimes non-existent&amp;ndash;budget. At times like these, we scour the web for quality free and cheap design assets. This post will share my favorite sources for free assets. They&amp;rsquo;re in no particular order, but I think they&amp;rsquo;re all pretty cool.
Pexels: Free Stock Photos and Video  Pexels  Though the free stock images are what brought me to Pexels in the first place, you can also find quality stock videos there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to KayEssPea Blog!</title>
      <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/02/27/welcome-to-kayesspea-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 11:08:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/02/27/welcome-to-kayesspea-blog/</guid>
      <description>Hello, and welcome to my new blog! I decided that I wanted a blog, and so here it is. This will predominantly be a design and web development blog. I love to teach, and I like to write. So, I figured there&amp;rsquo;d be no better place to write the things I want to teach!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using JavaScript Libraries for Game Development</title>
      <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/02/24/using-javascript-libraries-for-game-development-activateconf2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 14:07:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/02/24/using-javascript-libraries-for-game-development-activateconf2018/</guid>
      <description>This talk is about using JavaScript to create games on the HTML5 canvas. Though you won’t create the next Halo, you’ll learn so much about JavaScript and programming as a whole when you create games with it. In this talk, I’ll introduce you to a library that’s perfect for beginners and “non-coders” alike called p5.js.
Why JavaScript? JavaScript is everywhere. If you use the internet, you’ve almost certainly encountered JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>