<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on KayEssPea Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/categories/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on KayEssPea Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Keisha S Perkins</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 02:17:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.keishasperkins.com/categories/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How One PSD Transformed My Workflow</title>
      <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/04/03/how-one-psd-transformed-my-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 02:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/04/03/how-one-psd-transformed-my-workflow/</guid>
      <description>I create a good deal of media for my church, and sometimes that media needs to be used in many ways. Perhaps the event flier that I create for a pre-service loop of slides needs to also be made to fit social media, or be printed and handed out.
Up until recently I solved this issue by first designing something for the church&amp;rsquo;s presentation screen at a 16:9 ratio, then resizing and tweaking the design to meet whatever other needs where given to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Powerful Illustrator Shape Builder Tool</title>
      <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/04/02/the-powerful-illustrator-shape-builder-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 10:34:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/04/02/the-powerful-illustrator-shape-builder-tool/</guid>
      <description>When I began to foray into Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Creative Suite, I was using Photoshop for everything. Need a logo for lots of uses? Just deliver a huge PNG! Want to draw a nice crisp illustration? Photoshop&amp;rsquo;s pen tool works just fine for that, right?
Photoshop was my one-stop for everything I needed, though none of what I needed was what Photoshop was created for. It was some time before I even considered using any of Adobe&amp;rsquo;s many great pieces of software that actually suited my needs, like Illustrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Five Sources for Free Assets</title>
      <link>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/03/18/top-five-freebie-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 11:08:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.keishasperkins.com/2018/03/18/top-five-freebie-sources/</guid>
      <description>I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair to say that all of us have at one time or another needed to get a job done on a small&amp;ndash;or sometimes non-existent&amp;ndash;budget. At times like these, we scour the web for quality free and cheap design assets. This post will share my favorite sources for free assets. They&amp;rsquo;re in no particular order, but I think they&amp;rsquo;re all pretty cool.
Pexels: Free Stock Photos and Video  Pexels  Though the free stock images are what brought me to Pexels in the first place, you can also find quality stock videos there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>